// Questions for the quiz

const quizQuestions = [{
    question: "Which Disney Villain has a pet named diablo? ",
    answers: [
        {option: 'Cruella'},
        {option: 'Evil Queen'},
        {option: 'Maleficent'},
        {option: 'Ursula'}
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Maleficent'
},
{
    question: "In Cinderella, what is the name of the Tremaine family's black cat?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Cat"},
        {option: "Lucifer"},
        {option: "Mr. Diablo"},
        {option: "Evil"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Lucifer"
},
{
    question: "Which colour is Madam Mim's hair in Sword in the Stone?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Purple"},
        {option: "Blue"},
        {option: "Pink"},
        {option: "White"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Purple"
},
{
    question: "What did Ursula want from Ariel in The Little Mermaid?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Her hair"},
        {option: "Her voice"},
        {option: "Her eyes"},
        {option: "Her mind"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Her voice"
},
{
    question: "Which 90s Disney movie featured a fearsome villain called Frollo?",
    answers: [
        {option: "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"},
        {option: "The Lion King"},
        {option: "Beauty and the Beast"},
        {option: "Pocahontas"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
},
{
    question: "Who wants to be the fairest of them all?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Ursula"},
        {option: "Cruella"},
        {option: "Evil Queen"},
        {option: "Madame Mim"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Evil Queen"
},
{
    question: "Who's completely obsessed with fashion and fur?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Lady Tremaine"},
        {option: "Cruella"},
        {option: "Queen of Hearts"},
        {option: "Jafar"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cruella"
},
{
    question: "Jafar's last wish was to become a..?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Sultan"},
        {option: "Genie"},
        {option: "Snake"},
        {option: "Sorcerer"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Genie"
},
{
    question: "Shan-yu, the villain in Mulan, is the leader of the..",
    answers: [
        {option: "Philistines"},
        {option: "Barbarians"},
        {option: "Vikings"},
        {option: "Huns"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Huns"
},
{
    question: "What was the name of Zeus brother in Hercules?",
    answers: [
        {option: "Heron"},
        {option: "Hades"},
        {option: "Poseidon"},
        {option: "Ares"}
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hades"
}];